pips-fx.com 2016-03-25

# Privacy Policy|PIPSFX

The privacy of our clients is vital to PIPSFX. We understand the protection of personal information is very important, and take our security and maintenance of our traders’ privacy seriously.

We encourage you to read through our policy and to contact us with any questions.

Provisions contained within this notice apply equally to both current and former customers.

  1. Personal information.

We will require personal information when you activate a Live Account with PIPSFX, in order to supply you with the best possible service. This information is required in order to help us in processing your transactions and requests, evaluating your financial needs, keeping you informed about services and products of interest to you, retrieving lost passwords, and ensuring a complete customer service experience. The law also requires us to retain certain records.

  1. Information required may include the following:

Application information: full name, date of birth, identity or social security number, mailing address. It may also be required to ascertain occupation, income and assets, and other similar information, as detailed on the application forms.

Transaction information – records of past communications and information regarding your transactions with us or/and our affiliates, including trading activity, account balances, past communications and inquiries, and our responses.

Verification information – verification of your identity documentation (such as driving license or passport) may be necessary, as well as bank statement, utility bill, credit card copy, etc.

Note: It is required by the AML (Anti-Money Laundering) and the USA Patriot Act for financial institutions to collect information where deemed necessary and take action where appropriate, in order to confirm a customer’s identity.

Note: PIPSFX would like to make clear that they will not knowingly maintain or collect information of a personal nature from children under the age of 13.

If we become aware that we have been provided information from a child under 13 years-old, we will take the necessary actions to delete such information from our records.

We ask parents or guardians who become aware of his/her child providing personal information without their consent, to contact us at: [info@pips-fx.com](mailto:info@pips-fx.com)

  1. The use of cookies.

Pieces of textual information sent electronically from your webserver to your browser and stored to your computer are called “cookies”. PIPSFX collects and uses the information acquired from these. Note, cookies do not contain any personal information nor identify you individually, unless you have volunteered such information willingly – for example, when registering for an online service or opening an account. In order to identify and measure traffic patterns on the website, and to track performance of advertisements and web features, PIPSFX may use these cookies for this purpose.

This enables PIPSFX to understand how you and other users use web services and the PIPSFX website, giving us the ability to improve the functionality and navigation of our website. It also helps us to present the most useful information and offers to you.

Information garnered from these cookies may be shared with PIPSFX employees, affiliates, and agents. However, we do not sell information to any unaffiliated third parties.

When you visit the PIPSFX website, we may allow other companies or their 3rd party ad servers to set their own cookies on your browser. We recommend that you refer to the privacy policy of these companies if you are in any doubt as to their usage, but generally they use cookies in the same manner as PIPSFX.

  1. Sharing information.

All or some of the given personal information may be shared as detailed above with our affiliates. This is in order to inform clients of new services and products, as well as service client accounts. Our affiliates may include companies which have an ownership interest in our company, or which are owned or controlled by us. Your privacy of your personal information will be treated and maintained in the same manner and to the same extent by our affiliates as it is by PIPSFX, in accordance to the PIPSFX privacy policy.

  1. Third Parties.

Except from described within this privacy policy, PIPSFX does not disclose to any third parties your personal information. Disclosures to third parties might include sharing information with non-affiliate companies who carry out support services for your account. It may also include those who facilitate your transactions with PIPSFX. Also, this may involve companies who assist with legal, professional, or accounting services to our business. The extent to which non-affiliate companies who assist PIPSFX with services must maintain confidentiality of personal information is the same in which they receive it in. They are also obligated only to use your personal information in the course of providing said services and only for the purposes set out by PIPSFX.

There is the possibility that PIPSFX may disclose a customer’s personal information to a third party in the event they need to fulfill instructions or pursuant to express consent. Please note that PIPSFX will not sell your personal information.

As permitted by, or in order to apply to applicable regulations and laws, PIPSFX may need to disclose personal information provided to third parties. This can and may include disclosing personal information in order to comply or cooperate with law enforcement agencies or regulatory authorities, as and when may be required to protect our rights or property.

  1. Merger or bankruptcy.

Personal customer information will merge along with the company should a merger of PIPSFX take place. In accordance to its incorporation laws and the requirements of its recordkeeping, different legal statues shall apply in the event of bankruptcy.

  1. Payment information.

Customer’s credit card information is not kept in any form by PIPSFX.

Should you be required to provide a copy of your credit card, the CVC on the back of the card should be hidden and that only the last four digits of the card should be visible.

  5. Failure to provide personal information.

It is your choice whether you provide any or all of the personal information required by PIPSFX. However, it should be noted that any missing information could result in our company being unable to maintain or open an account for you. This may also affect our ability to provide you with our services.

  6. Opt out.

An email sent to our email address: [info@pips-fx.com](mailto:info@pips-fx.com)  will be necessary in order to have your name and personal data removed from our database. Please understand that any missing information could result in our inability to open or maintain an account for you, and /or to furnish you with our services.

  7. Amendments.

Users will be notified via email and within a reasonable timeframe should our privacy policy be subject to any amendments that affect the personal information of our users collected on our website. Users have the option of whether or not we use the information in a different manner. All other amendments by us which do not affect the user’s personal information will be updated to our website.

  8. Mailing Information.

At PIPSFX we have someone here to help you, 24/7, should you require to talk to us in regards to our privacy policy or any other issue. We can be reached via phone, fax, mailing address, or email. A customer service representative can also be IM’d via our chat facility.

**Registered Address:  
**Keyds Lydya Ltd  
Marshall Islands, office address Trust Company Complex, Ajeltake  Road, Ajeltake Island, Majuro, Marshall Islands, MH 96960  

**Mailing Address:  
**KEYDS UK LIMITED  
2 Woodberry Grove, Finchley, London, N12 0DR, ENGLAND  
**Phone:** +44.20.35.192.667  
**Email:**  [info@pips-fx.com](mailto:info@pips-fx.com)

This Privacy Policy is in effect from 18.07.2014.
